amrullohrobbani@gmail.com | +62 899 948 748 22 | linkedin.com/in/muhammad-amrullah-robbani

SUMMARY

Voracious full-stack web developer who specializes in front-end aspects for 4 years and enthusiastic biomedical engineer with proven skills in ideation, creation, and leadership in 1 internship and several biomedical engineering projects. Interested in biomedical data integration and optimization in sports or eSports to enhance player performance and coaches' knowledge. Led front-end team to refactor company CSR website to increase customer engagement up to 800 users and completed 4 biomedical engineering projects: non-invasive glaucoma detection, wearable ECG, teenager fitness data acquisition, and non-invasive fetal electrocardiogram.

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi Bandung Indonesia (2015-2019) - Bachelor of Engineering, majoring in Biomedical Engineering (GPA: 3.14)

ITB is one of the top universities in Indonesia in Natural Sciences and Engineering & Technology.

- Developed a full-stack website for managing hospital assets and warehouse for Ministry of Health of Malaysia Project
- Developed an electrode for wearable electrocardiogram vest and full stack website and cloud to manage, analyze and display ECG data
- Received Asrama Salman Scholarship 2016 and 2017
- Received YBP PLN Scholarship

EXPERIENCE

Bioelectricity Based Fetal Movement Detector (Freelance Project) Research Engineer

Bandung, Indonesia

July 2021 – Present

 Designed and experimented on biomedical instrumentation of bioelectricity based fetal movement detectors for everyday use and collaborated with midwives to develop mobile, user-friendly, precise instrumentation.

Robovis Laboratory (Biomedical Engineering Laboratory in Institut Teknologi Bandung)

Bandung, Indonesia

- Research Assistant

 Designed and experimented on biomedical instrumentation for everyday use and collaborated with doctors to develop
- Developed a non-invasive glaucoma detection to acquire and analyze EEG signal and detect glaucoma then display the
 result on a website.
- Developed a non-invasive fetal electrocardiogram to obtain fetal heart signal and analyze the outcome.

Suteki Tech (Education Technology Solutions Startup)

mobile, user-friendly, precise instrumentation.

Bandung, Indonesia

Front End Engineer

Mar 2022 – Present

- Led a front end team in Company CSR Project and developed a website to manage college students and synchronize data to The Ministry of Education, Culture, Research, and Technology Indonesia with up to 800 university users.
- Designed and created company source control documentation to increase and optimize company main web product source control

E-Life Solution Plt Malaysia (startup consulting firm for technology solutions)

Johor, Malaysia

Front End Engineer Intern

May 2018 – Jul 2018

Received return offer at the end of internship

- Worked with a team of other developers on built hospital assets and inventory management systems
- Designed indoor positioning system for hospital assets utilizing Internet of Things
- Develop and build a front-end website to manage, analyze and display assets and inventory usage on the hospital

Databugar.itb.ac.id (Joint Project of three department in Institut Teknologi Bandung)

Bandung, Indonesia

Website Developer and Consultant

Feb 2019 – Present

As a web development project leader, planned, managed, and supervised the teenager fitness data Management web
development, coordinated with the design team, and presented to the client of 2 high school and entire first-year of the
university.

Regista (Sport GPS tracker and athlete management startup)

Bandung, Indonesia

Founder

Feb 2019 – Present

Designed and developed a sport GPS tracker for football players to track player vital and performance assessment tools.

Vent-I Ventilator Indonesia (COVID ventilator project by Masjid Salman ITB)

Bandung, Indonesia

Calibration Engineering Volunteer

Mar 2019 – Jun 2019

- Designed prototype calibrator for newly designed ventilator and High Flow Nasal Cannula (HFNC) for COVID 19.
- Conducted ventilator calibration and organized related documents to optimize HFNC production cost.

ORGANIZATIONAL ACTIVITIES

President - Pusat Teknologi Tepat Guna (Pustena)

Dec 2015 - Jul 2018

- Revitalize club and establish club foundation by collecting and implementing important document to plan and extends club life for 4 years
- Recruited 7 new members and designed new training curriculum to develop new member in technology aspects

Syiar Chief - Panitia Pelaksana Program Ramadhan (P3R) Salman ITB 1438 H

Dec 2016 - Jul 2017

 Led a team to plan and coordinate a Ramadhan Event with up to 20% member performance increase and client satisfaction.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Certifications: Passed level C1 of CEFR by getting 7.5 overall band score on IELTS **Skills:**

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, VueJS, NuxtJS, NextJS, PostgreSQL, Nginx
- Data Processing: Python, TensorFlow, Google Suite
- Design: Adobe Photoshop, Krita, Manga Studio
- Language: English

Interests: Biomedical Engineering, Biomechanics, Web Development, Data Analysis in Sport and E-Sport